

NONTAWAT NASUKKA

PROFILE

Address : Plum Condo Central Station Phase 1 15 Ratchadaphisek Rd Sao Thong Hin Sub district

Bang Yai District, Nonthaburi 11110

Date of Birth: 11/05/1998

Age: 26 year Height: 175 cm Weight: 62 kg Nationality: Thai Gender: Male Religion: Buddhism

CONTACT

Tel: 062-5978322

E-mail: nontawat.1stace@gmail.com

Line: firsts009

Facebook : Nontawat First Github : 1st-Nontawat

Web contect: https://profile-nontawat.netlify.app

SKILLS

microsoft 365

Python HTML CSS

C++

javaScript TypeScript Node.js

React Docker Flutter Git

Database: MongoDB, MySQL, SQL postgres

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Speak English fair level Write English fair level Reading English fair level

OBJECTIVE

i want to apply knowledge to develop further. The amount is beneficial to the organization and increases the efficiency of work in the future.

EDUCATIONAL

BANGKOK UNIVERSITY 2017-2021 Bachelor's degree.Faculty of Engineering. Electrical Engineering GPA: 3.29

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kumwell Corporation PLC

(13 February 2024 - 31 August 2024)

Design & software Engineer

- -Control cabinet design
- -User Manual
- -Coding IOT
- -Testing Code product by Node-red

DECHAPANICH FISHING NET FACTORY LIMITED

(7 March 2022 - 23 December 2023)

R&D engineering

- -control cabinet design
- -Design lighting systems, Emergency & Exit lights, Recaptacle
- -Write a PLC program for Mitsubishi

ACHIEVEMENT

License for Professional Practice (Associate Electrical Engineer) Driving license private car Certificate Full Stack Developer by FutureSkill Certificate basic software engineer by Udemy